

# **Luka Trailovic**

Frontend Web Developer

# **CONTACT INFO**

trailovicluka@outlook.com

+47 92 95 97 99

trailovic.dev

Oslo, Norway

#### **EDUCATION**

School: SS Mladost Graduated: 06/2015 Degree: Paralegal

# **SKILLS**

**HTML** 

CSS

**JavaScript** 

**TypeScript** 

React.js

Next.js

**TailwindCSS** 

**JSON** 

**APIs** 

**ShadCN** 

Three.js

Github Firebase

Authorization

Slack

Figma

Adobe CC

Vercel

Docker

Linux

# **ABOUT ME**

Professional Web Developer with 5+ years of experience in React.JS, with a passion for creating top-quality, modern, minimalistic solutions, following the latest standards of the industry. My focus is on interactive, user-friendly interfaces that meet the client's needs. As a friendly and kind person, I make a great team player.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### LEAD DEVELOPER

DGold Systems 12/2022 - 10/2023

Led a team of developers in creating an enormous network of apps, that included virtual currencies, a banking app, robotics startup, company's ecological initiative, and other. Day-to-day duties included:

- Reviewing pull requests;
- Streamlining communication between frontend and backend teams;
- Meeting with teams to discuss projects;
- Negotiating with 3rd party providers;
- Coordinating between the teams and the company directors;

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

DGold Systems 07/2021 - 12/2022

Worked in a team of developers to build a number of landing pages, web apps, including a video conferencing app that brought 75.000 new members to the project. My part in collaboration included:

- Styling components using Tailwind;
- Integrating APIs, such as Agora API;

# **PERSONALITY**

Detail-oriented

Creative

Communicative

Adaptable

Curious

**Patient** 

Methodical

Reliable

Analytical thinker

# **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

In my free time, I enjoy taking long walks around the beautiful city of Oslo. I am an avid reader, especially mystery and crime novels. I play the guitar, and I love music. I used to play football, and still like to catch a game on TV. I often use my free time to catch up on the latest news and updates in the world of programming and like to learn new skills and programming languages.

# **LANGUAGE**

Serbian – Native English – Fluent Norwegian – Learning

- Collaborating closely with backend team;
- Keeping apps and systems up-to-date;
- Developing a virtual currency;
- Translating pages to various languages;

#### **WEB STORE DEVELOPER**

Freelance 02/2020 - 06/2021

Developed, published and maintained web stores for various clients. One of the clients made record sales via web store, enabling them to open two new physical stores. Some responsibilities included:

- Hosting the client's store;
- Updating plugins in WP stores;
- SEO;
- Al chat integration;
- Regular updates on thousands of prices;
- Developing user zones and databases;

# OTHER EXPERIENCE

# **PARALEGAL**

JW Belgrade Branch – Legal Dept 03/2019 – 02/2020

Volunteered in a legal office specialized in human rights and freedom of speech and religion. My work mosty constituted of drafting contracts and other legal documents. As for my achievements, I digitalized a 100-year old library, and started the creation of an office museum.